Nevada Folklife Archive
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  - Subseries 1: Audiocassettes
    - Juanita Simmons, talking about Fordyce Club in Las Vegas and nationwide network of support for former residents or people associated with Fordyce, Alaska. Recorded at the Palace Station, Las Vegas, July 11, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-003; Blanton Owen; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Toni Schutte (Larry Schutte in background) about her apprenticeship in horse hair hitching with Doug Krause, apprenticeship has not yet begun. Recorded at Schutte's home in Tuscarora, August 8, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-004; Blanton Owen and Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Eddie Brooks; saddlemaker, master artist in 1989-1990 FAA Program. Also present are Alan McDonald (apprentice) and Andrea Graham, August 31, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-005; Blanton Owen and Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Alan McDonald (apprentice with saddlemaker Eddie Brooks). Andrea Graham is also present, August 31, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-006; Blanton Owen and Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Spider Teller and Ira Walker at Spider's saddle shop. Spider is master and Ira is apprentice. FAA 1989-1990. Bill Fox is also present, October 4, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-007; Blanton Owen and Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Doug Krause (master) and Toni Schutte (apprentice) about horsehair hitching, November 3, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-008; Blanton Owen; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Art Cavanaugh (master) and Steve Kane (apprentice) on Paiute-Shoshone songs. Night time, around campfire at Steve's sweat lodge on Reno Indian Colony land north of Reno (Hungry Valley?) hand drum playing and singing, December 21, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-009 - C-1989-010; Blanton Owen; 1 sound cassette
    - Albert Biale, November 5, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-011 - C-1989-012; Blanton Owen; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Victoria and Camille Pradere of Dayton, November 9, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-013 - C-1989-014; Andrea Graham and Blanton Owen; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Louis Gibellini in Prospect, November 12, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-015; Andrea Graham and Blanton Owen; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Pete Delmue at Delmue Ranch, November 13, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-016; Andrea Graham and Blanton Owen; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Benny Damele at Dry Creek Ranch, December 7, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-017; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with John and Roberta Damele in Eureka. Roberta Damele's father Peter Merialdo was interviewed by the University of Nevada, Reno Oral History program in Reno, December 10, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-018 - C-1989-019; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Louis Gibellini in Eureka, November 4, 1989, AFC 2017/002: C-1989-020 - C-1989-021; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Norma Williams and Stacy Gibbs about buckskin tanning and smoking, August 28, 1990, AFC 2017/002: C-1990-001; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Florine Conway, Tamara Crawford, Teresa Jackson about Washoe baskets, August 30, 1990, AFC 2017/002: C-1990-002; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Jean Pierre Pedrini about saddle making, September 23, 1990, AFC 2017/002: C-1990-003; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Basque Singing Festival: San Francisco Basque Choir, the Bertsolaris, Jesus Gonea, Martin Goigochea, Johnny [?], Jesus Arreada, and several unidentified singers, April 20, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-001; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Jesus Larrea (master), Lisa Corcostegui (apprentice). Apprenticeship in Basque dancing, September 10, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-002; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Ranching, cowboy poetry; person interviewed was Mike Prince, October 12, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-003 - C-1991-004; 2 sound cassettes
    - Apprenticeship in Shoshone beadwork with Angie McGarva (master) and Tamea Knight (apprentice), November 9, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-005 - C-1991-006; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Apprenticeship in Washoe basketry with JoAnn Martinez (master) and Cynthia Foster Rodriguez (apprentice), November 23, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-007 - C-1991-009; Andrea Graham and Elaine Thatcher; 3 sound cassettes
    - Mormon religion, December 12, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-010; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Tom Martinet, a craps table box man, at his home in Las Vegas. Gaming, compulsive gamblers, antisocial nature of gambling, violence attracted by gambling, November 10, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-011 - C-1991-012; Lesley Williams; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Maxine Mansor, felt maker at her home in Boulder City. Process of felt making, Mansor's background in art, November 19, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-013; Lesley Williams; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Lois Mack on southern cooking; Louisiana upbringing, at Cuthbert Mack's law office, Las Vegas, December 2, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-014; Lesley Williams; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Olga Carbia, Andres Vargas, South American musicians at Nevada Business Service, Las Vegas, December 3, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-015; Lesley Williams; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Kennard Johnson, a Navajo fashion designer, December 5, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-016; Lesley Williams; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with railroad man, Jeff McColl, December 6, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-017 - C-1991-018; Lesley Williams; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Monique and Samuel "Smash" Johnson; Tahitian and Hawaiian musicians, December 8, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-019 - C-1991-020; Lesley Williams; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with hoop dancer, Chris Anderson, his father Leroy and his mother at their home on the Moapa Indian Reservation, December 10, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-021 - C-1991-022; Lesley Williams; 2 sound cassettes
    - African American writer and poet, Nancy Ellen Webb Williams, December 11, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-023 - C-1991-024; Lesley Williams; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Birdie Ford, Irdell Clark at the E.O.B. Senior Center, talk of glass blowing; making artist's renditions of signs into reality, December 12, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-025 - C-1991-026; Lesley Williams; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Tomiyo Kazama, a Japanese Samarai song and karaoke teacher, December 13, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-027; Lesley Williams; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with the Harris Sisters, African American gospel singers, Las Vegas, December 15, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-028; Lesley Williams; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with neon sign maker, Mark Willett, November 1, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-070; Russell Frank; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with neon sign maker, Don Beck, November 1, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-071; Russell Frank; 1 sound cassette
    - Meet and auction, Darwin's Magic Club at Pat's Chinese Restaurant, Las Vegas, November 7, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-072 - C-1991-073; Russell Frank; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Gray Darwin about his career as a magician, November 9, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-074 - C-1991-075; Russell Frank; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Abel Sedeno at Sedeno's Neon Shop about his career in neon sign making, November 12, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-076; Russell Frank; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Jerry Monger about life on the Union Pacific Railroad, November 18, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-077 - C-1991-079; Russell Frank; 3 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Art Laurie about life on the Union Pacific Railroad, November 19, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-080 - C-1991-081; Russell Frank; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Ray Leitner about poker and magic, November 22, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-082 - C-1991-083; Russell Frank; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with woodcarver, Roy DeVicente, at Main Street Station, Las Vegas, November 24, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-084 - C-1991-085; Russell Frank; 2 sound cassettes
    - Gary Darwin's magic act, intro by Lou Simonoff, November 25, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-086-A-B; Russell Frank; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview at IHOP with Brian Guerin on driving a cab in Las Vegas. Ambient restaurant noise on tape, December 5, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-087; Russell Frank; 1 sound cassette
    - Hanukkah party at Temple Beth Shalom, featuring cantor Gary Golbart, December 5, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-088; Russell Frank; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with magician Daniel Cros about magic, December 9, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-089; Russell Frank; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Gary Golbart about his life as a cantor and a performer on the Strip in Las Vegas, December 11, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-090 - C-1991-091; Russell Frank; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Pete Barbutti about his career as a comic-musician, December 13, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-092 - C-1991-093B; Russell Frank; 3 sound cassettes
    - Friday night service led by cantor Gary Golbart at Temple Beth Shalom, December 13, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-094 - C-1991-095; Russell Frank; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Patty Syms about glass engraving, December 15, 1991, AFC 2017/002: C-1991-096 - C-1991-097; Russell Frank; 2 sound cassettes
    - Hawaiian crafts, February 12, 1992, AFC 2017/002: C-1992-001; 1 sound cassette
    - Side A: Amauta rehearsal, Side B: Harris Sisters rehearsal, May 23, 1992, AFC 2017/002: C-1992-002; 1 sound cassette
    - Dean Barlese song of a social dance red star at Fort Bidwell, California. Song structure - Dean Barlese, June 28, 1992, AFC 2017/002: C-1992-003; 1 sound cassette
    - Schurz Pine Nut Festival, September 19, 1992, AFC 2017/002: C-1992-004; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Schurz Pine Nut Festival, Round Dance songs and blessing ceremony, September 19, 1992, AFC 2017/002: C-1992-005 - C-1992-006; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Native American Program at Moapa High School in Overton, December 11, 1992, AFC 2017/002: C-1992-007; 1 sound cassette
    - Aana Mitchell (master), Diana Ohata-Sims (apprentice), Hawaiian crafts, December 14, 1992, AFC 2017/002: C-1992-008 - C-1992-009; 2 sound cassettes
    - Hester Katzman, Jewish stories, December 15, 1992, AFC 2017/002: C-1992-010-; 1 sound cassette
    - Andy Manzanares, New Mexican music, December 15, 1992, AFC 2017/002: C-1992-011 - C-1992-012; 2 sound cassettes
    - Las Vegas Scots Pipe Band, January 11, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-001; 1 sound cassette
    - Japanese taiko drum, February 9, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-002; 1 sound cassette
    - Alex Kalavsos Greek music, February 10, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-003; 1 sound cassette
    - Adam Fortunate Eagle, Chippewa stone pipe making, March 28, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-004; Blanton Owen and Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Theresa Jackson (master), apprenticeship in Washoe basketry, Sue Coleman (apprentice), April 17, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-005; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Dean and Heidi Barlese apprenticeship in powwow singing, July 9, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-006; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Evelyn Pete, Edna Mike, Lilly Sanchez about Shoshone willow basketry and culture. Interview at Evelyn's house with her sisters Edna and Lilly, October 16, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-007 - C-1993-008; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Pat Kanoknata, Santhana Lopez. Thai classical dance apprenticeship. Pat (master), Santhana (apprentice), December 5, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-009; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview Zoria Zetaruk, Natalie Pruc, Luba Eads, on Ukrainian Easter eggs at Zoria's house. FAA 1994, December 6, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-010; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances. Side A: Introduction to Las Vegas Folklife Festival; performance by hoop dancer Chris Anderson and other Southern Paiute dancers. Side B: Performance by steel drum player Rupert Henry and the Caribbean Stars, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-011; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival interview and performances: Side A: Performance of Paraguayan music on harp and guitar (Cesar Daniel - harp; Tito Martinez - guitar), Side B: Performance of Thai classical dance by Pat Kanoknata and his students, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-012; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Ethiopian Mutual Association of Nevada, Side B: St. John's Greek Orthodox Church Dancers, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-013; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Performance by Warburton Family Bluegrass Band, Side B: Performance of African American gospel music by Victory Baptist Church Choir, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-014; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Performance by Amauta, a South American musical ensemble, Side B: Performance of Hawaiian and Polynesian dance and music by Hula Halau O Kaho'onei, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-015; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Performance of Hawaiian and Polynesian dance and music by Hula Halau O Kaho'onei, Side B: Performance by African American drill team, the Poisonettes, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-016; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Performance by cowboy poet Mike Prince, Side B: Performance of Jewish storytelling by Hester Katzman, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-017; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Workshop by Amauta, South American musical ensemble, Side B: Presentation on gambling lore by Tom Martinet, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-018; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performance: Side A: Presentation on gambling lore by Tom Martinet (last four minutes), May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-019; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Presentation on dowsing by members of the Desert Dowsers, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-020; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival interview: Side A: Interview of Dr. Tom Clark (University of Nevada, Las Vegas English professor and expert on the language of gambling), by Dorothy Wright, May 1, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-021; Dorothy Wright; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Becky Eagle (Rebecca Eagle Lambert), June 6, 1993, AFC 2017/002: C-1993-022; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Oscar Carrescia (master) at Oscar's studio. Oscar worked with Olga Carbia (apprentice) teaching Argentinean guitar, April 7, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-001; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Lilly Sanchez, June 16, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-002; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview Amy Barber, Jody Barber Steele, Washoe willow basketry apprenticeship, June 21, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-003; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Oscar Carrescia (master) and Olga Carbia (apprentice) on Argentinean folk guitar, at Oscar's studio. Andres Vargas, Nelson and Judith Rodriguez are also present, September 20, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-004; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interviewed Tongan Congregation at the Sunday service at First United Methodist Church, October 2, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-005 - C-1994-006; Eliza Buck; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Jesse Hall, music director for the Interfaith Gospel Choir practicing at Second Baptist Church, October 2, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-007 - C-1994-008; Eliza Buck; 2 sound cassettes
    - Dan Price silver work, bits, spurs, October 4, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-009 - C-1994-010; Eliza Buck; 2 sound cassettes
    - Don Brandfas and Terry Wilson talk about magic and magicians and do demonstrations at The Magic Shop, October 5, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-011 - C-1994-012; Eliza Buck; 2 sound cassettes
    - Visha Siddharthan talking about Bharata Natya career; also practice with students at Visha's home, October 6, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-013; Eliza Buck; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Greg "Lightning" Williams about auctioning; actual auction, October 8, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-014; Eliza Buck; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Reverend Cary Anderson at AME Sunday church service, October 9, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-015 - C-1994-016; Eliza Buck; 2 sound cassettes
    - H.B. McCay talks about cowboying, horse shoeing, and horses; shoeing demonstration, October 10, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-017 - C-1994-018; Eliza Buck; 2 sound cassettes
    - Tongan Congregation, Sione Motu'Ihala. Choir practice in the large home of the lay minister where community meets nightly, October 12, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-019; Eliza Buck; 1 sound cassette
    - Colin Sendall talks about dowsing, also tells stories of World War II service, October 12, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-020; Eliza Buck; 1 sound cassette
    - Tape made by musician. Collection of songs sung by Leland Smith, sent to Eliza Buck, undated, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-021; Eliza Buck; 1 sound cassette
    - Manuel Ramirez Hernandez interviewed at Bertha Miranda's restaurant about career; sample of typical songs, October 13, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-022; Eliza Buck; 1 sound cassette
    - Karen Burns, showgirls, October 14, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-023 - C-1994-024; Eliza Buck; 2 sound cassettes
    - Nancy Jackson, African American hairstyles, October 15, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-025; Eliza Buck; 1 sound cassette
    - Norm and Bernie "Sam" DeLorme, at their home, talking about traditional weaving, harvesting, games, other traditional practices, October 16, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-026 - C-1994-027; Eliza Buck; 2 sound cassettes
    - At home of Tony and Lily Steele, talking about circus, trapeze flying, entertainment, October 16, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-028 - C-1994-029; Eliza Buck; 2 sound cassettes
    - Diwali Festival at Billinghurst Middle School, November 5, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-030; Tamara Layman; 1 sound cassette
    - Second Baptist Church, congregation members, November 6, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-031 - C-1994-032; Tamara Layman; 2 sound cassettes
    - Eddie Brooks (master) and Alan McDonald (apprentice) talking about the saddle making apprenticeship, September 28, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-033 - C-1994-034; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Edward McDade talks about buckskin tanning and glove making, September 29, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-035; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Mohamed Barrie (master, from Sierra Leone) and Eric Jackson (apprentice) rehearsing at a dance studio in North Las Vegas. African drumming apprenticeship, October 26, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-036 - C-1994-037; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Native American music and dance by hoop dancer Chris Anderson and the Rainbow Shield, Side B: Paraguayan music by Cesar Daniel (harp) and Zino Delvalle (guitar) singers and dancers, April 24, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-038; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: South American music by Amauta, April 24, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-039; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Demonstration of dowsing by members of the Desert Dowsers, Side B: Workshop on South American music by Amauta, April 24, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-040; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival performances: Side A: Music and dance by Japanese American Citizen's League, Kaminari Taiko Drummers, Ondo Dancers; African American gospel by Meltonettes quartet, Side B: Hawaiian and Polynesian music and dance by Hula Halau O Kaho'onei, April 24, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-041; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival: Side A: Performance of Jewish stories by Hester Katzman. Performance by African American drill team the Poisonettes, Side B: Performance by Warburton Family Bluegrass Band, April 24, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-042; 1 sound cassette
    - Reno Celtic Festival, November 6, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-043; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Supatra Chemprachum, November 17, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-044; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Virginia McCuin, November 17, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-045; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Farida Kuraishy (Kuranshy[?]), December 3, 1994, AFC 2017/002: C-1994-046; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview Lilly and Virginia Sanchez at Lilly's house in Stillwater about Shoshone basketry. Virginia's baby daughter Cora is also there, January 14, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-001 - C-1995-002; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Doug Muraoka, Norma Honda-Wagoner, about Japanese taiko drumming apprenticeship; at Doug's apartment, January 17, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-003 - C-1995-004; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Interview with Edward McDade and Lyle Sam. Buckskin tanning apprenticeship; recorded at Ed McDade's house in Lee. His wife, Florine McDade is also present, January 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-005; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Malick Sow (master) apprenticeship in African Drumming, Abayomi Goodall (apprentice), October 26, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-006; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Madelina Henry (master) Renee Aguilar (apprentice), Washoe acorn biscuits, November 28, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-007; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Manuel "Popeye" McCloud and Marlin Thompson on Paiute singing apprenticeship, December 6, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-008 - C-1995-009; Andrea Graham; 1 sound cassette
    - Interview with Elizabeth Brady, Lois Whitney, food workshop at Cowboy Poetry Gathering. Side A and B: Presentation of Shoshone cooking workshop at Cowboy Poetry Gathering. Elizabeth Brady is Lois Whitney's mother; both live at the colony in Elko, January 25, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-010 - C-1995-011; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Herbal medicine workshop at Cowboy Poetry Gathering. Side A and B: Presentation on traditional herbal medicine by Eva Castellanoz, Mexican American from Nyssa, Oregon, and Reggie Sope, Shoshone from Duck Valley, Nevada, January 25, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-012 - C-1995-013; Andrea Graham; 2 sound cassettes
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival: Side A: Performance of Hawaiian hula by Las Vegas Hawaiian Civic Club Gracious Ladies, Side B: Performance of Thai classical dance by Thai Cultural Arts Association, April 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-014; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Side A: Performance of Paraguayan music by Cesar Daniel (harp) and Tito Martinez ( guitar and vocals), Side B: Performance of Ethiopian dance by Ethiopian Mutual Association of Nevada, April 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-015; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Side A: Performance by Japanese American Citizen's League Kaminari Taiko Drummers and Ondo Dancers, Side B: Performance of Native American music and dance by Rainbow Shield Singers and Dancers and hoop dancer Chris Anderson, April 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-016; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Side A: Performance of Hawaiian hula by Ports of Paradise Hawaiian Dance Academy, Side B: Performance of Filipino dance by Philippine American Youth Organization, April 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-017; 1 sound cassette
    - Las Vegas Folklife Festival, Side A: Performance of South and Central American music by Amauta, Side B: Workshop on South and Central American music by Amauta, April 22, 1995, AFC 2017/002: C-1995-018; 1 sound cassette